[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of  Team Americas computer, featured in the movie Team America: World Police?", "correct_answer": "I.N.T.E.L.L. I.G.E.N.C.E.", "incorrect_answers": ["It has no name", "Dell", "Super Computer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the tallest waterfall in Asia?", "correct_answer": "Hannoki Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["Midagahara Falls", "Shomyo Falls", "Toyama Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1949 movie won Oscar for Best Picture?", "correct_answer": "All the Kings Men", "incorrect_answers": ["Bridge On the Rover Kwai", "Lawrence of Arabia", "Ben Hur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which part of the human body is the so-called Pouch of Douglas located?", "correct_answer": "Pelvis", "incorrect_answers": ["Aorta", "Stomach", "Duodenum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the end of the film The Big Lebowski, The Dude finally receives a replacement rug.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Peladophobia is the fear of this type of people.", "correct_answer": "balding people", "incorrect_answers": ["sexual predators", "gang members", "trash collectors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flag of Luxembourg consists of three vertical stripes of red, blue, green.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is sometimes called Eulers Formula.", "correct_answer": "e^(pi*i)+1=0", "incorrect_answers": ["a^2+b^2=c^2", "e=m*c^2", "a^2=b^2+c^2-2*a*b*cosine c"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The human brain has approximately 14 billion cells.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What caused the tragedy with the Saudia Flight 163 on August 19, 1980?", "correct_answer": "Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["The pilot fell asleep.", "Fog", "A bird"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What decade did the pop culture icon the plastic lawn flamingo come into existence?", "correct_answer": "60s", "incorrect_answers": ["40s", "30s", "80s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Memento premiered on this film festival.", "correct_answer": "Venice Film Festival", "incorrect_answers": ["Toronto Film Festival", "Sundance Film Festival", "Deauville Festival of American Film"]}]